#### ABOUT ME

I am an Automation Specialist transitioning to a **Full Stack Developer** role.

I have completed courses in Java programming and JavaScript/React.

To deepen my knowledge and apply new skills, I am working on a personal project focused on financial management that incorporates both backend and frontend technologies.

# FILIP POLITOWSKI

+48 785 106 215



### **COURSES**

07.2023 - 10.2023

JavaScript Specialist: React + Redux

CodersLab

12.2022 - 07.2023

**Java Developer** 

CodersLab

## **SKILLS/TOOLS**

- Java
- OOP
- Spring
- Hibernate
- JUnit
- MySQL/Postgres
- REST API
- IntelliJ
- Git
- Docker

- HTML5, CSS, JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- VS Code
- Operating Systems Windows/Linux
- Working with documentation
- Teamwork
- Project work
- English level B2

# **EDUCATION**

02.2018 -11.2019

**Gdańsk University of Technology** 

2nd Degree Course

**Automation, Robotics and Control Systems** 

Informatics in Control Systems

10.2014 - 02.2018

**Gdańsk University of Technology** 

1st Degree Course

**Automation, Robotics and Control Systems** 

**Automation and Control Systems** 

Link to my project on GitHub, which I am currently working on: https://github.com/Filip-Politowski/WealthVoyage

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

10.2018 - present Automation Engineer

Zaczarowany Ołówek, Juszkowo

- Creation of technical documentation
- Creation of technical drawings and 3D models in Fusion 360
- Development of prototype projects
- Design of electrical diagrams in SEE Electrical
- Selection of components for designed devices
- Design and 3D printing of models
- Preparation of project quotations
- Implementation of projects in accordance with CE directives
- Assembling designed devices
- Participation in meetings with foreign contractors
- Providing technical support to customers, including at automation fairs
- Proficient in Fusion 360, SEE Electrical, Galileo, CODESYS, and PrusaSlicer

07.2017 - 08.2017 Internship

Maintenance Department

Zapolex Sp. z o.o., Toru

- Creating service documentation for printing machines
- Daily problem-solving during breakdowns
- Working with wiring diagrams and technical documentation
- Collaborating with the maintenance team

#### **HOBBY**

Bike (gravel/bikepacking) Computer games (soulslike) Programming (web)

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (UE) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of the personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).